



Chester Springs, Pennsylvania 19425



4254952453

brittany.klose@yahoo.com

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Bachelor of Science

Marketing The University of Tampa Florida May 2021

- Summa cum laude graduate
- Dean's List 2019-2021
- Senator & Co-Marketing Director for Society of Collegiate Leadership and Achievement (SCLA)
- Phi Kappa Phi active member

LPS Coding Bootcamp

University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, PA Expected in May 2022

Social Network

UPenn

- APIS behind a social network application. Create accounts, post thoughts, and react to friends.
- Technologies: Express.js, MongoDB database, Mongoose ODM
- Video Demos on my github page!

BRITTANY KLOSE

SUMMARY

University of Tampa graduate and current UPenn bootcamp coder! Expanding my skills in technology and UI to provide the ultimate user experience. Check out my portfolio page and Github profile!

- LinkedIn: brittany-klose
- https://britt-klose.github.io/Portfolio-Klose/
- https://github.com/britt-klose

SKILLS

- Languages: HTML, JS, CSS, Node.js, Graphql, Mysql, Nosql, Handlebars
- Technologies: VS Code, Bootstrap, GitHub, Server-Side APIs, GitBash, MERN, React, IndexDb,
- Team Collaboration
- Data Collection and Analysis
- Campaign Development

EXPERIENCE

MARKETING MANAGER

Four's A Crowd | Remote, PA | September 2021 - Current

- Manage all social media platforms and design new content using Canva.
- Promote and market upcoming seasons of the show.
- · Network with local companies to sell ad space

MARKETING INTERN

Megabuck Enterntainment | Philadelphia, Remote | July 2021 - Current

- Design content and visuals for email campaign via Mailchimp, and evaluate success.
- Network with up in coming Spotify artists to write songs and join record label.
- Craft social media posts to market for new sales and engage audience.

FRONT DESK AGENT

Holiday Inn Express | Exton, PA | June 2019 - December 2020

- Customer service: Assisted guests and managed billing information
- Maintained relationships between employee departments, and guest

Company Database

UPenn

- Database of company roster.
 Add, delete and update employees, departments, managers, and more!
- Languages: Node.js, JS, Mysql
- https://github.com/brittklose/Company-Database-12

Online Music Store

UPenn

- Perfect example of the coding behind Ecommerce. Browse, add, delete, and checkout items.
- Languages: HTML, CSS, JS, Nodemailer, Bootstrap, Mysql, Node.js, Handlebars
- https://mortal-instrumentsmusic-shop.herokuapp.com/

IB Diploma

Business STEM Academy, Downingtown, PA May 2018 conflicts/problems

MARKETING ASSISTANT

Montgomery County Chamber of Commerce | King of Prussia, PA | June 2019 - January 2020

- Engaged in cold calling to promote upcoming events.
- Acted as liaison with members to verify information and update CRM systems.
- Created and disseminated member profiles.

MARKETING INTERN

PayPal | Conshohocken, PA | December 2018 - January 2019

- Collaborated with Sr. Management in web design and digital marketing to incorporate customer engagement into digital processes.
- Trained on customer engagement and service standards regarding branding and customer behavior.
- Participated on sales calls.
- Was coached on upselling and cross selling techniques.

INTERN

Saul Ewing Arnstein & Lehr LLP | Philadelphia, PA | January 2019 - December 2018

- Consulted with marketing department on customer retention and loyalty.
- Coached on the dynamics of marketing and branding in paralegal industry.